Guide to the James H. Fraser papers, 1898-1999 and undated RL.11790
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
James H. Fraser papers
1898-1999 and undated
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Fraser, James H. (James Howard), 1934-2013
RL.11790
7.0 Linear Feet
James Howard Fraser was a librarian, archivist, scholar and author; Director of the Florham-Madison Library at Fairleigh Dickinson University in New Jersey. The James Fraser papers include photographs and slides, articles, correspondence, brochures and pamphlets, magazines, clippings, reprints and other printed material primarily relating to outdoor advertising and graphic art. Subjects covered include activities in support of war efforts (World War I and World War II), anti-billboard and -advertising controversies, outdoor advertising industry promotion, and discussions of advertising as art. Institutions represented include the Advertising Council (and its precursor, War Advertising Council), General Outdoor, Foster & Kleiser, O.J. Gude, Outdoor Advertising Association of America, Poster Advertising Association and Thos. Cusack Co. Acquired as part of the John W. Hartman Center for Sales, Advertising & Marketing History.
Arrangement
Organized into the following series: General Files; Printed and Published Materials; Photographs, Slides and Graphic Designs
Biographical / Historical
James Howard Fraser was a librarian, archivist, scholar and author; Director of the Florham-Madison Library at Fairleigh Dickinson University in New Jersey. Fraser was born in 1934. He received a Doctorate in Library Science from Columbia University (1972) and worked at Fairleigh Dickinsin University from 1970 until his retirement in 2001. Fraser was a specialist in children's literature (editor of the scholarly journal Phaedrus); graphic arts and outdoor advertising (published The American Billboard: 100 Years in 1990). Fraser served as archivist for the Outdoor Advertising Association of America (OAAA) Archives at Fairleigh Dickinson until it was transferred to Duke University beginning in 1996. Fraser died in 2013.
Access Restrictions
Collection is open for research.
Provenance
The James H. Fraser papers were received by the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library as a gift in 2015.
Related Materials
Related materials may be found in the following Hartman Center collections:
Advertising Council records
Burr L. Robbins papers
General Outdoor Advertising Company plan books
John Paver papers
Naegele Advertising records
Outdoor Advertising Association of America (OAAA) Archives
United War Work Campaign
War Effort Mobilization Campaigns poster collection
Collection Overview
The James Fraser papers include photographs and slides, articles, correspondence, brochures and pamphlets, magazines, clippings, reprints and other printed material primarily relating to outdoor advertising and graphic art. Subjects covered include activities in support of war efforts (World War I and World War II), anti-billboard and -advertising controversies, outdoor advertising industry promotion, and discussions of advertising as art. Institutions represented include the Advertising Council (and its precursor, War Advertising Council), General Outdoor, Foster & Kleiser, O.J. Gude, Outdoor Advertising Association of America, Poster Advertising Association and Thos. Cusack Co. Acquired as part of the John W. Hartman Center for Sales, Advertising & Marketing History.
Advertising, Outdoor; World War, 1914-1918; World War, 1939-1945; Billboards -- United States -- History; Posters, American -- 20th century -- United States; John W. Hartman Center for Sales, Advertising & Marketing History; Outdoor Advertising Association of America; General Outdoor Advertising Co; Foster and Kleiser Company; Poster Advertising Association; Advertising Council; War Advertising Council
- General Files, 1923-1996 and undated; 1
  - Advertising as art, 1923-1952 (Box 1)
  - Bibliography of outdoor advertising collection at Fairleigh Dickinson, 1981 (Box 1)
  - Correspondence, 1957-1996 (Box 1)
  - Correspondence--Joseph Blackstock, 1964-1996 (Box 1)
    Scope and Contents
    Joseph Blackstock was Director of Research at Foster & Kleiser.
  - List of billboard artists, undated (Box 1)
  - National Poster Competition, 1948 (Box 1)
  - OAAA archives at Fairleigh Dickinson, 1986 (Box 1)
  - Outdoor advertising clippings compiled by Garrett Orr, 1955-1987 (Box 1)
  - Outdoor advertising history--Clippings and notes, 1924-1991 (Box 1)
  - Outdoor advertising history--Notes, 1990 (Box 7)
  - Outline of a textbook, undated (Box 1)
  - Slideshow text--The Wall-Dog Era, undated (Box 1)
  - Top outdoor advertisers, 1956-1986 (Box 1)
- Printed and Published Material, 1901-1997 and undated; 2
  - Advertising Agency, 1958 (Box 1)
  - Advertising & Selling--Annual advertising awards, 1940 (Box 1)
  - Advertising Council--Statement of Functions and Objectives, undated (Box 1)
  - Advertising Federation of America--Facts You Should Know About Anti-Advertising Propaganda in School Textbooks, 1939 (Box 1)
  - Advertising Media Value of the On-Premise Sign (Walter Meyers), 1974 (Box 1)
  - Affichage (France), 1979, 1987 (Box 7)
  - American Advertising Museum brochure, 1996 (Box 1)
  - American Artist, 1942 (Box 1)
  - American Civic Association--Important Advances Toward Eradicating the Billboard Nuisance, 1920 (Box 1)
  - ARE Media (Sweden)--Promotional material (in Swedish), 1968 and undated (Box 1)
  - Art of Advertising Outdoors (Hal Stebbins), 1958 (Box 1)
  - Associated Billposters and Distributors constitution, 1906 (Box 1)
  - Associated Outdoor Advertisers of New Jersey--Outdoor Advertising: A Vital Service to New Jersey Business, 1930 (Box 1)
  - Behind the Signs, 1947 (Box 1)
  - Bennett College--Advertising and Sales Management (chapter from reference library), 1925 (Box 7)
  - Big Picture, 1995 (Box 1)
  - Billboard Museum of America--Corrrespondence, 1989-1991 (Box 1)
  - Billboard Museum of America--Letters to the museum, 1989 (Box 1)
  - Billboard Museum of America--Meeting agendas and minutes, 1989-1990 (Box 1)
  - Billboard Museum of America--Proposal and Request for Space to establish the museum, 1989 (Box 1)
  - Billposter, 1901 (Box 1)
  - Billposter and Distributor, 1907 (Box 7)
  - Billposter-Display Advertising, 1901-1907; 6 folders (Box 1)
  - British Poster Advertising Association (Great Britain)--How It (BPAA) Came About (Cyril Sheldon), 1950 (Box 1)
  - British Poster Advertising Association (Great Britain)--One Hundred Years of Poster Advertising, 1929 (Box 1)
  - British Poster Advertising Association (Great Britain)--Posters magazine, 1930 (Box 1)
  - Bryan Company--Ohio's Greatest Billposters and Outdoor Advertisers, 1910 (Box 1)
  - Catalog Design (K. Lonberg-Holm and Ladislav Sutnar)--Chapter "Posters", 1944 (Box 7)
  - Chicago Association of Commerce--Exhibit brochures, 1931-1935 (Box 1)
  - Clipping on Dan Walsh, dealer in propaganda posters, 1986 (Box 1)
  - Cushman's Sons--Our New Brooklyn Bakeries and Our Advertising, 1920 (Box 1)
  - Das Plakat (Germany)--Tables of contents, 1918-1920 (Box 1)
    In German. Das Plakat was Europe's premier graphic arts and design magazines.
  - Does Outdoor Advertising Gain Response?, 1936 (Box 1)
  - Donaldson Lithographing--Big Guns in Banking, 1928 (Box 1)
  - Edwards & Deutsch Lithographing--Munsingwear poster promotional, 1920s (Box 7)
  - Eller/Pacific--The Best in 10 Words or Less, 1978 (Box 1)
  - Ervine Metzl articles, 1962 and undated (Box 1)
    Includes: America and Posters; Eight Great Posters
  - Federal Highway Administration--Outdoor Advertising Control and Acquisition, 1981 (Box 1)
  - Financial Advertisers Association--Outdoor Advertising for Banking, undated (Box 1)
  - Forbes Lithograph--Making Posters Human and Keeping 'Em That Way (Merle Penney), undated (Box 7)
  - Forbes Lithograph--Planning Posters for Maximum Results (Merle Penney), 1939 (Box 1)
  - Forbes Lithograph--Poster Production (Merle Penney), 1948 (Box 1)
  - Foster & Kleiser--Analysis and Review of the Highway Advertising Situation, 1928 (Box 1)
  - Foster & Kleiser--Company history (Joseph Blackstock), 1986 (Box 1)
  - Foster & Kleiser--Publications, 1926-1979 and undated; 2 folders (Box 1)
    Includes: Ad Andy in Outdoorland (coloring book); Art as Big as All Outdoors; Description of a New and Improved Method of Hanging Posters on Modern Advertising Structures; Everything You Always Wanted to Know About the Poster But Were Too Afraid to Ask! (Debi Matthews); Forty Years of Advertising; Our News; Outdoor Advertising; Painted Bulletins; Poster Design (W.T. Warde); Strip Artists (Matt Groenig)
  - Foster & Kleiser--Walter Werde designs, 1940s-1950s (Box 7)
    Walter Werde was General Art Director of Foster & Kleiser
  - Foster & Kleiser--Walter Werde index to outdoor advertising designs, 1913-1952 (Box 1)
  - Foster & Kleiser--Walter Werde writing, speech, undated (Box 1)
    Includes: The Idea's the Thing; What Makes Good Outdoor Advertising Art?
  - General Foods--Salesgrams, 1940 (Box 7)
  - General Outdoor Advertising Company--Company history, 1940 (Box 1)
  - General Outdoor Advertising Company--Painted walls, 1920s (Box 7)
    Includes: Kitchen Klenzer; Polarine motor oil; Red Crown gasoline
  - General Outdoor Advertising Company--Promotional materials, 1920-1957; 2 folders (Box 1)
    Includes: GOA General News; Streamliner designs; The GOAL: General Outdoor Advertising Life
  - General Outdoor Advertising Company--Publications, 1928-1931 (Box 7)
    Includes: Chicago The Great Central Market; The GOAL General Outdoor Advertising Life
  - Graphic Design (Leon Friend and Joseph Hefler)--Chapter "The Poster", 1936 (Box 7)
  - Graphic Design in America, 1990 (Box 1)
  - Harveys Advertising and Billposting Company (Shanghai China)--Publicity Advertising in the Far East, 1913 or 1914 (Box 1)
  - Highway Aesthetics: New Directions for Outdoor Advertising (Richard Hill), 1970 (Box 1)
  - History of Advertising Trust (Great Britain)--Journal of Advertising History 8, 1984 (Box 1)
  - History of Outdoor Advertising (Donald Herdon), undated; 2 folders (Box 1)
  - How I Produce Motion Picture Posters (Carlos de la Vega, Mexico; text in English, posters in Spanish), 1952 (Box 1)
  - Institute of Outdoor Advertising--Awards/Obies, 1965-1992; 3 folders (Box 1)
  - Institute of Outdoor Advertising--Common Sense: Key to Good Outdoor Advertising, 1975 (Box 1)
  - Institute of Outdoor Advertising--Outdoor America, undated (Box 1)
  - Institute of Outdoor Advertising--Publications, 1974-1982 (Box 1)
    Includes: Best of Outdoor; Outdoor: The Media's Medium; The Big Outdoor; The First Medium
  - Instructor--That Truth About Advertising May Prevail in Our Schools, 1940 (Box 1)
  - International Chamber of Commerce (France)--Who Sees Outdoor Advertising?, 1958 (Box 1)
  - Ivan B. Nordhem Co.--The Nordhem Poster, 1918 (Box 1)
  - Joseph Schlitz Brewing Co.--Address to the American Federation of Advertising by Dean James McCarthy (Notre Dame), 1946 (Box 2)
  - Lionel--Miniature billboards for train sets, 1950 (Box 2)
  - McCandlish Lithograph Corporation--The Making of a 24-sheet Poster, 1940s (Box 2)
  - McCann-Erickson--13 Steps, 1941 (Box 2)
  - McCann-Erickson--Poster Awards, 1936-1937 (Box 2)
  - Mediacom (Canada)--Great International Poster Advertising, undated (Box 2)
  - Memorandum on the Work of the War Advertising Council, 1942-1943 (Box 2)
  - Metromedia Technologies--As the Drum Turns, 1990 (Box 2)
  - Metromedia Technologies--Outdoor Bulletins on Demand, 1988 (Box 2)
  - Milwaukee Advertising Club--The Torch, 1946 (Box 2)
  - Model Railroader--Article on billboards for train sets, 1993 (Box 2)
  - National Conference on Planning--Planning and Civic Commitment, 1942 (Box 2)
  - National Outdoor Advertising Bureau--Publications, 1923-1943 and undated (Box 2)
    Includes: Lexicon of Terms Commonly Used in Outdoor Advertising; Outdoor Advertising--General Information; The Bureau-gram
  - National Poster Art Alliance--Poster art contest, undated (Box 2)
  - National Sign Association--Service Sheets, 1940-1941 (Box 2)
  - New America That's Coming, 1956 (Box 2)
  - Newell-Emmett Company--Current Production: A Review of Our Recent Work for Clients, 1940 (Box 7)
  - New York Subway Advertising Company--Promotional series, 1940s (Box 2)
  - Nigerian Government Posters: Visual Records of People and Progress (Sibyl Moses), 1980 (Box 2)
  - North Carolina survey of outdoor sign sniping, 1920s-1930s (Box 2)
  - O.J. Gude Company--Outdoor Advertising Display, 1920 and undated (Box 2)
  - Old Dutch Cleanser--Bachelor's Children (Bess Flynn), 1939 (Box 2)
  - Oliver Dennett Grover feature (Lilias Bill), 1923 (Box 7)
  - Outdoor Advertising Associates--Out-Door Advertising, 1925 (Box 2)
  - Outdoor Advertising Association of America (OAAA)--1912-1952 Federal Litigatons (Box 2)
  - OAAA--Advertising Progress newsletter, 1926-1927 (Box 2)
  - OAAA--Case study: Blue Boy, 1938 (Box 2)
  - OAAA--Case study: Blue Boy, 1938 (Box 7)
  - OAAA--Case study: The Chief, 1941 (Box 2)
  - OAAA--History of OAAA, 1986 (Box 2)
  - OAAA--In the Public Interest, 1941 (Box 2)
  - OAAA--OAAA News index, 1951-1954 (Box 2)
  - OAAA--OAAA News War Activities Souvenir Edition, 1945 (Box 7)
  - OAAA--OAAA officers, department rosters, 1953-1963 (Box 2)
  - OAAA--Outdoor Advertising, 1931 (Box 2)
  - OAAA--Outdoor Advertising: A Channel of Communication in the War Effort, 1942-1944 (Box 2)
  - OAAA--Outdoor Advertising History and Regulation, 1969 (Box 2)
  - OAAA--Outdoor Advertising News, 1956, 1963 (Box 2)
  - OAAA--Outdoor Story, 1954, 1961 (Box 2)
  - OAAA--Painted displays, 1928-1932 (Box 2)
  - OAAA--Pamphlets, 1990-1991 and undated (Box 2)
    Includes: Beauty and Utility in Outdoor Advertising; Billboard Basics; Centennial Convention brochure
  - OAAA--Poster Art as an American Art Form (A.E. Germer), 1942 (Box 2)
  - OAAA--Proceedings: Outdoor Advertising Association Sales School, 1930 (Box 2)
  - OAAA--Public relations reports, 1927-1933 (Box 2)
  - OAAA--Publications, 1928-1994; 2 folders (Box 2)
    Includes: Art and Outdoor Advertising; Billboard Basics; Billboards The Clean Medium; Books list; Copy ideas; Economics of Outdoor Advertising; How to Use Outdoor Advertising in a Political Campaign; Landscape Manual for Outdoor Advertising; Modern Outdoor Advertising Policies and Practices; Public Relations in Outdoor Advertising; Resolution Recommended by the Censorship Committee (tobacco advertising appealing to women and children); Staehle Humanizes Animals
  - OAAA--Report of public service campaigns, 1948-1964 (Box 2)
  - OAAA--Sales Tickler, 1929 (Box 2)
  - OAAA--Theme song, 1930 (Box 2)
  - OAAA--Tour Through an Outdoor Advertising Plant, 1950s (Box 7)
  - OAAA--War Time/Victory Time newsletters, 1943-1947 (Box 2)
  - Outdoor Advertising Associaton of New York--100 Reformers vs. 25,000 Wage Earners, 1939 (Box 2)
  - Outdoor Advertising Incorporated--"Circulation" promotional, 1930s (Box 7)
  - Outdoor Advertising Incorporated--Indoors and Outdoors for Greatest Sales Results, 1950s (Oversize-folder 1)
  - Outdoor Advertising Incorporated--Legal, 1931 (Box 2)
  - Outdoor Advertising Incorporated--Pamphlets, 1957 and undated (Box 2)
    Includes: Indoor/Outdoor; "Picture Window" brochure
  - Outdoor Advertising Incorporated--Presentation of the Plan for the Formation of OAI, 1931 (Box 2)
  - Outdoor Advertising Incorporated--Publications, 1937-1940 (Box 2)
    Includes: Jantzen case study; L.M. Clark experimental poster study; Out of the Mouths of Babes
  - Outdoor Advertising Incorporated--Reprints, 1939-1941 (Box 2)
    Includes: Catch 'Em Out of Doors (J.A. Brogdon); Words Fail Me (Kerwin Fulton)
  - Outdoor Advertising Progress 1896-1926, 1946 (Box 7)
  - Outdoor Network/USA--Superflex brochure, undated (Box 2)
  - Outdoor Publicity (Great Britain), 1952 (Box 7)
  - Pacific Coast Poster Advertising Association--Minutes, 1921 (Box 2)
  - Painted Outdoor Advertising Association--Promotional binder, 1924 (Box 2)
  - Patrick Media--Impressions magazine, 1988 (Box 7)
  - Patrick Media--Premier Panel brochure, undated (Box 2)
  - Poster Advertising Association--How to Use Poster News (Burton Harrington), 1924 (Box 2)
  - Poster Advertising Association--Plant Classification manual, 1913, 1919 (Box 2)
  - Poster Advertising Association--Poster News, 1923-1925 (Box 2)
  - Poster Advertising Association--Publications, 1912-1922 (Box 2)
    Includes: Convention brochures; Educational Posters; Poster Advertising series; Why the Association
  - Poster Parts Company--Non-Wrinkle (posting process), undated (Box 2)
  - Poster Production Fund--Here Are 54 Posters You Can Sell Now, undated (Box 2)
  - Poster Scene, 1988-1990 (Box 2)
  - Posters from Contemporary China (Len Rubenstein), 1980 (Box 2)
  - Posters in an Exhibition (Christopher Trump; WWI poster exhibit from Louis Cowan Collection), 1975 (Box 2)
  - Printers' Ink reprints, 1924 (Box 2)
    Includes: How Outdoor Advertising Can Be Part of the Natural Landscape (Franz Aust); Meal Ticket of American Art (James O'Shaughnessy)
  - Private Visions, Public Art (Carol Stevens), 1987 (Box 2)
  - Promotion Bureau--The Stamp of Approval from Billposters Throughout the U.S. and Canada (testimonials), 1910 (Box 2)
  - S.D. Warren Company--Posters Used by American Industries as War Production Incentives, 1942 (Box 2)
  - S.D. Warren Company--Selling with the Help of Direct Advertising, undated (Box 2)
  - Sheldons Limited (Leeds, England)--What "Service" Means in Billposting, 1916 (Box 2)
  - Signs of the Times, 1931-1985; 27 folders (Box 3)
    Includes some sample issues, but mainly excerpts: articles, font and typography examples; index/tables of contents
  - Signs of the Times, 1997 (Box 4)
  - Skywriters See It This Way (C.B. Colby), 1947 (Box 4)
  - Society for Electrical Development--Electrical advertising brochure, 1928 (Box 4)
  - Society for Electrical Development--Suggested Uniform Ordinance, undated (Box 4)
  - Space to Let: Plan for Advertising in a New Town (Kenneth Browne), 1957 (Box 4)
  - Striking the Right Note in Advertising (Bella Landauer), 1951 (Box 4)
  - Supplement to The Advertising World (exhibit of British advertising), 1914 (Box 4)
  - Taking Art to the People Through Outdoor Advertising (Loredo Taft), 1920s (Box 4)
  - The Poster, 1913-1929; 2 folders (Box 4)
  - The Poster--Commodity File, 1923 (Box 4)
  - The Poster--Reprints, 1924-1928 (Box 4)
    Includes: Advertising Essential to Business (Henry Mueller); Bringing Art to the Home Town (Loredo Taft); If Standard Outdoor Advertising Did Not Exist! (E.J. Costello); The Democratization of Art (Franz Aust)
  - The Poster as a Force in War and Peace (on WWI posters), 1976 (Box 4)
  - The Role of Roadside Advertising in American Business, 1940s (Box 4)
  - The Values of Art in Advertising (Franz Aust, Robert Harrison), 1930 (Box 4)
  - The Xth Olympiad: An Outdoor Advertising Opportunity, 1931 (Box 4)
  - Thomas Cusack Company billboard examples, 1923 and undated (Box 4)
  - Tresors Art Fair to Feature 200 Shanghai Posters from 1900-1930 (Claudette Peralta), 1994 (Box 7)
  - Tri-City Posting Service--Script for "Case History" traffic safety program, 1947 (Box 4)
  - Tribute to Kerwin Holmes Fulton (Myles Standish), 1954 (Box 4)
  - U.S. Department of Commerce--Advertising and Its Role in War and Peace, 1943 (Box 4)
  - U.S. Treasury Department--Minute Man newsletter, 1945 (Box 4)
  - VMSD (Visual Merchandising and Store Design), 1997 (Box 4)
  - Walker & Company anniversary feature, 1935 (Box 4)
  - Walter Hill's Billposting Department Limited (London, England)--Catalog of hoarding sites, 1913 (Box 4)
  - War Advertising Council--Home Front Campaigns, 1945 (Oversize-folder 1)
  - War Advertising Council--Savings Bonds poster, 1942 (Oversize-folder 1)
  - War Advertising Council--They Are Taking Away the Sandbags, 1944 (Box 7)
  - Western Lithograph--Color Illusions (Archie Vazquez), undated (Box 4)
  - What I Learned from a Poster Board (sermon by Rev. R.B. Dear), 1924 (Box 4)
  - Women's Fact-Finding Roadside Association report, 1941 (Box 4)
  - World War I--United War Work Campaign, 1918 (Box 4)
  - World War II--Publications, 1941-1946; 2 folders (Box 4)
    Includes: A Report on the Use of War Objective Copy by National Users of Outdoor Advertising--A Channel of Communications in the War Effort; Reference to the Army and Navy in Advertising; The [War Advertising] Council Looks Ahead; War Theme Digest
- Photographs, Slides and Graphic Designs, 1898-1999 and undated; 3
  - Photographs and Graphic Designs, 1898-1999 and undated; 1
    - Appliances, utilities, 1920-1940 (Box 5)
    - Automotive--Cars and trucks, 1912-1987 (Box 5)
    - Automotive--Gas, oil, parts, 1920-1970 (Box 5)
    - Beverages, 1913-1980s (Box 5)
    - Candy, 1923-1930 and undated (Box 5)
    - Clothing, 1920-1990 (Box 5)
    - Dr. Seuss characters in outdoor advertising, 1930s (Box 5)
    - Food and condiments, 1913-1976 (Box 5)
    - Food--Bread, cereal, crackers, 1913-1946 and undated; 3 folders (Box 5)
    - Foster & Kleiser--Billboard structure designs, 1930s (Box 5)
    - Foster & Kleiser--Christmas designs, 1934 (Box 5)
    - Foster & Kleiser--Walter T. Warde advertising designs and sketches, 1930s-1940s; 6 folders (Box 5)
    - Health and cosmetics, 1913-1934 (Box 5)
    - Health and cosmetics--Palmolive, 1913-1930 and undated (Box 5)
    - Household and miscellaneous, 1920-1976 (Box 5)
    - International, 1931 and undated (Box 5)
    - Locations, 1890s-1977; 2 folders (Box 5)
    - Media, 1914-1990 (Box 5)
    - New York (Broadway, Times Square), 1911-1954 (Box 5)
    - Outdoor advertising companies, 1914-1990 (Box 5)
    - Parker Pen, 1948 and undated (Box 5)
    - Public service messages, 1919-1979 (Box 5)
    - Real estate, 1926 and undated (Box 5)
    - Soap and cleansers, 1910-1930 (Box 5)
    - Tobacco, 1913-1999 (Box 5)
    - Tobacco--Camel (includes World War II-era), 1913-1954; 3 folders (Box 5)
    - Tobacco--Lucky Strike, 1920s-1930s (Box 5)
    - Tobacco--Prince Albert, 1913-1947 (Box 5)
    - Tobacco--Winston, 1954-1955 (Box 5)
    - Transportation and travel, 1916-1977 (Box 5)
    - War time, 1898-1960s (Box 5)
  - Slides, 1915-1994 and undated; 2
    - Presentations and loose slides, 1915-1994 and undated; 17 folders; 22 folders (Box 5)
    - Presentations and loose slides, 1915-1994 and undated; 6 folders (Box 6)
  - Negatives, undated; 3
    - Loose negatives, undated; 2 folders (Box 6)